<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nimilou</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page1_title">Welcome to Nimilou!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page1_desc">Welcome to Nimilou. This app allows you to listen to audio stories. It supports interactive story formats like Telmi, which lets you navigate through the stories with ease.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page2_title">Add story Pack</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page2_desc">To use the app, you need to connect with a community that will help you find story packs to add to the app. Telmi-format pack listings can be added from the configuration page in the "Pack Sources" tab. Some links to communnnity already added to the app:</string>
    <string-array name="onboarding_page2_links">
        <item>https://monurl.ca/lunii.creations</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="onboarding_page3_title">Add story</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page3_desc">After that, you can download packs and add them to the app using the "+" button in the Pack tab. The packs must be in ZIP format.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page4_title">Add story</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page4_desc">Depuis l\'onglet "Pack distant" dans la configuration, vous avez la possibilité de télécharger des histoires libres de droits du groupe "Raconte moi une histoire"</string>
    <string name="please_add_pack_in_settings_menu">Please add pack in settings menu</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="please_add_pack">Please add pack</string>
    <string name="no_pack_in_source_or_bad_source">No pack in source or bad source</string>
    <string name="ajout_d_une_liste_de_pack">Add packs list</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_title">Disclaimer :</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_content">The application you are using allows access to audio stories. Please be aware that you are solely responsible for verifying the origin and validity of the sources of the stories you download, share, or listen to through this application. Ensure that the content is free of copyright or that you have obtained the necessary permissions to use it. The application cannot be held liable for any copyright infringement or violation of intellectual property rights.</string>
    <string name="custom_source">Custom sources</string>
    <string name="default_source">Default sources</string>
</resources>